hi guys it's almost the end of the 19th
2019 market as a year where people or
and more people use their mobile devices
to do different things like shopping
ordering food booking a cab booking a
ride and also basically shopping for
goods and food like you know Sharpie
Lozada there's grab food there's foot
Panda so people now use the phone is not
just about Facebook or calling but also
it's now like the main shopping happened
of the days generation yes and 2020 that
trend will not change in 2020 in fact
more and more stuff will can be bought
using our apps using our phone next year
right do you think do you agree I'm sure
you'd be so but you know the end of the
year also marked us a year our time that
we plan for what's gonna happen next
year well 2020 is really a lot spacious
here it's a nice unit that's a nice ring
to it and I'm sure a lot of people are
now making preparing some of their new
your solution Aleutians what do you want
to do next year me probably what I'll be
more active blue suede yes you want to
prepare for next year but how prepared
you really are you for 2020 right so
when it comes to gold site we always
like to have instant results we want to
hit the fast-forward button and how
about in insurance do you think there's
a fast-forward button for insurance
without actually in 2020 you can do
you can actually buy insurance using
your smartphone via the fast-forward
button for insurance FWD so FWD is
offering different services under
website that you just can purchase
insurance without basically with no
paperwork just input all the information
needed on the website and pay on your
website using by a debit card or credit
card and Europe and you are covered so
if you want to learn more about this one
watch this video some of the biggest
hassle guys in buying insurance
sometimes is that you know you have to
have your medical check-up but there are
people who doesn't like any new one
instead you just want to be covered no
apps
nobody and you want it done fast you're
just like when you heard their food
you just want big food that you like
then pick your location and it will be
something you'll write so for insurance
well you didn't actually buy insurance
online now so let's head to FWD car comm
the pH data you will be taken to their
website and you can it be by online
so let's buy online so let's buy
Oh Oh the things you can do we when
we've got you so well so now it's now
hassle-free
with FWD can buy online in minutes so so
basically they have three can do plans
and so can do so you can do it now so
first we have the can do pen which is a
protection against forty two critical
illnesses and you don't need any medical
tests plus you have six months only
telemedicine rewards you can call a
doctor doctor doctor asked questions
right this is nice can do been the other
net the next plan is what you call can
do life so life insurance coverages can
live so can live is it's a two hundred
thousand live insurance coverage with
one year unlimited consoles rewards so
let's learn more about this one yes so
you have an event us you'll be copper a
be the event those clinics will be will
be available for to help you when it
comes to if you have any questions that
comes to you know help
and finally if you're into travel like
like the kids these days or you travel a
lot we have an insert five hundred
thousand accident a terrorism coverage
and they call it can guard yes so you
pay out for accidents or terror attacks
it's a worldwide coverage plus one year
global emergency see services work so
Wow so everything is covered so you know
what all these plans by the way is only
one seven nine nine and that's the whole
ear coverage already so 179 is
practically 150 a month or less than
five pesos a day
awesome awesome right and hours are
available here in FWD so let's
let's continue what if I'm gonna buy now
let's say let's go to can man by now
then you will be asked to ask for
details so you fill it up up then after
sending your ID and then you have cash
surrender value there are more and some
declarations you just have to check and
that's the basic plan it's one 799
annual payment up to 55 years old and
above and you're covered from any 42
covered critical illnesses and the sum
assured is 100,000 pesos and afterwards
you just gonna click confirm and pay use
your debit card credit card and voila
your cover
easy right easy isn't it amazing guys
wow it's so powerful now I mean here are
three good reasons why I'm gonna get a
candle plan now it's in now one it's a
good insurance coverage I mean can you
imagine it's a hundred thousand for
critical illness 20 thousand for life
insurance and five hundred thousand for
you know the accident and terrorism
coverage wow those are really good deals
and second number two it's
fast real a bit fast we love it instant
and you know we're just filling up
filling up your information and paying
it via your credit card you just have
you can now have an insurance coverage
in minutes and finally the third great
reason is price it's affordability 1 7 &
each where each can do plan it's like
investing 5 pesos every day to get such
amazing coverage so are you interested
see you better visit FWB that calm that
bh to buy your own plan or even to learn
more about it you can actually chat with
them if you visit their website so let
me know guys if you're interested and if
you have any questions that I can answer
yes I'll do my best spot the best thing
you can do also it's just visit their
site because it's not easy and thank you
so much for watching guys and have a new
Happy New Year because this new year we
can do a lot of great things let's move
forward FWD it's fun